An Inventory of the Elbridge Durbrow papers, 1926-1996
Hoover Institution Archives
- Khrushchev report on Moscow Conference, photocopy, 1961 (Box 71)
- Durbrow remarks at the Air Command and Staff College Allied Officers Graduation Ceremony, 1972 (Box 71)
- Security and Intelligence Foundation by-laws, undated (Box 71)
- Charles S. Via, biographical data, undated (Box 71)
- Ambassador James E. Nolan, Jr., biographical data, undated (Box 71)
- Autograph file, undated. (Box 71)
  Contains photocopies of prominent figures' signatures, Ronald Reagan, Franklin D. Roosevelt and Harry S. Truman
- "Urban Guerrilla Warfare," by Robert Moss, 1971 (Box 71)
- "Negotiate a Vietnam Political Settlement?" by Durbrow, undated (Box 71)